Guide to the Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive 1961-2009 (bulk 1976-2005) MSS.171
Fales Library and Special Collections
- ACCRETION 2014 - Series I: Artists Files
  - Bergman, Hartung, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Berlant, Tony, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Bermont, David, 1970 February (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Berthot, Jake, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Beuhler, Launa, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Biggs, Janet, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Birch, Willie, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Bochner, Mel, 2006-2007 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Boepple, Willard, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Borofsky, Jonathan, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Butler, Jim, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Cantor, Iris and B. Gerald, undated (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Center for Contemporary Graphic Art, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Chemical Bank Gallery, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Close, Chuck, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Coach, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Coutts Contemporary Art Foundation, 1992-2000 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - The Critical State of Visual Art in New York, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Crown Point Gallery, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Dade County, undated (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Daedalus Gallery, undated (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - David Beitzel Gallery, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - DeCarava, Roy, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Deutsche Bank North America, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - DiRobilant, Tristano, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 46)
  - Dia: Beacon, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - Dill, Lesley, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - Diller, Elizabeth and Ricardo Scofidio, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - Dumas, Marlene, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 50)
  - Edwards, Benjamin, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 51)
  - Equitable Center, undated (Box 58, Folder 52)
  - Evans, Cliff, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 53)
  - Fenley, Karen, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 54)
  - Finkel, Alan, undated (Box 58, Folder 55)
  - First Banks Art Program, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 56)
  - Fischer, Rob, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 57)
  - Fonseca, Ciao, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 58)
  - Fonseca, Gonzalez, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 59)
  - Francis, Sam, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 60)
  - Frankenthaler, 2000-2001 (Box 58, Folder 61)
  - Freud, Lucian, undated (Box 58, Folder 62)
  - Friedman, Tom, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 63)
  - Frost Art Museum, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 64)
  - General Mills Art Collection, undated (Box 58, Folder 65)
  - Gfeller, Catherine, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 66)
  - Gipe, Lawrence, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 67)
  - Gold, Lucas Samaras, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 68)
  - Good, Francie Bishop, 2001, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 69)
  - Hamada, Hiroyuki, undated (Box 58, Folder 70)
  - Hamasaka, Wataru, 1985-1996 (Box 58, Folder 71)
  - Hammond, Jane, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 72)
  - Hashimoto, Tadashi, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 73)
  - Hegge, James, 2001 November-December (Box 58, Folder 74)
  - Held, Al, 1973, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 75)
  - Hicks, Sheila, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 76)
  - Highstein, Jene, undated (Box 58, Folder 77)
  - Hockney, David, undated (Box 58, Folder 78)
  - Hodgkin, Howard, undated (Box 58, Folder 79)
  - Hofmann, Hans, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Holmes, Kathleen, 1993, undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Honert, Martin, undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - IBM Gallery of Science and Art, 1988, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - International Sculpture Center, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Ireland, Patrick, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Japan [1 of 2], 1995, undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Japan [2 of 2], 1995, undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Joan T. Washburn Gallery, 1998 October 22-December 19 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Johns, Jasper, 1986, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Kozloff, Joyce, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Lambert, Yvon, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Lawton, Pamela, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Lee Harris Pomeroy Associates, undated (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Leger, Fernand, 1994 February (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Lin, Maya, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - List Art Center, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - The Lobby Gallery, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Louden, Sharon and Kathleen McCarthy, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Lutz, Winifred, undated (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - MTA, undated (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Mapplethorpe, Robert, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Marden, Brice, 2007 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Marian Goodman Gallery, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Marisol, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Marx, Marcia, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Masson, Andre, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Metzher, Sheila, 2000-2005 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Milles, Carl, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Minkowitz, Norma, undated (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Miss, Mary, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Modern Master Tapestries, Inc., 1974, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Moore, Henry, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - Morrisseau, Norval, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Motyl-Palffy, Viola, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - Murrill, Gwynn, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Museum fur Moderne Kunst, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1983 January-1984 January (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Museum Tinguely, undated (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - New York City, 1990-2002 (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Opie, Julian, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Orozco, Gabriel, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Ossorio, Alfonso, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 45)
  - Otterness, Tom, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 46)
  - Paladino, Mimmo, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 47)
  - Paik, Nam June, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 48)
  - Pardo, Jorge, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 49)
  - Parsons School of Design, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 50)
  - Penck, A.R., 1985 (Box 59, Folder 51)
  - Pepper, Beverly, undated (Box 59, Folder 52)
  - Pfaff, Judy, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 53)
  - Poirier, Anne and Patrick, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 54)
  - Polke, Sigmar, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 55)
  - Porter, Katherine, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 56)
  - Posner, Richard, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 57)
  - The Progressive Corporation, 1990, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 58)
  - Public Art Dialogue=Southeast, 1989 June 8-11 (Box 59, Folder 59)
  - Public Art Fund, 1991-1992, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 60)
  - Richter, Gerard, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 61)
  - Rollins, Tim, Aldo Rossi, and K.O.S., 1991 (Box 59, Folder 62)
  - Rosenquist, James, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 63)
  - Rubins, Nancy, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 64)
  - S.I.T.E. (Sculpture in the Environment), undated (Box 59, Folder 65)
  - Samaras, Lucas, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 66)
  - San Francisco, undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Santa Fe, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Scagna, Italo, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Schroth, Peter and Josette Urso, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Seattle, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Shafrazi Gallery, 1990 May-June (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Shea, Judith, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Sheldon Memorial Art Gallery, undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Shelton, Peter, 1977-1982 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Shibata, Toshio, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Shonibare, Yinka, 2005-2006 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Silverthorne, Jeanne, undated (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Smith, David, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Kiki, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Richard, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Seton, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Smon, Branko, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Spanierman Gallery, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Solomon, Rosalind, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Sonnier, Keith, undated (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Steir, Pat, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Stella, Frank, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Stern, Oona, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Sternfeld, Joel, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Stockholder, Jessica, 1995-1996 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Storm King Art Center, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Stuart, Michelle, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - The Studio Museum in Harlem, 1989-1990 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Surls, James, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Sze, Sarah, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Taho, Ritsuko, undated (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Tawney, Lenore, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Taylor, Mary, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Thater, Diana, 2001-2002 (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Tomaselli, Fred, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Truitt, Anne, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Tucker, William, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - University of Houston, undated (Box 60, Folder 38)
  - Venet, Bernar, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 39)
  - Visual Arts Journal, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - Vivant, Pierre, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 41)
  - West, Franz, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 42)
  - Wolf, Silvio, undated (Box 60, Folder 43)
  - Women's Caucus for Art, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 44)
  - Woodman, Betty, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 45)
  - The World Financial Center, 1988-1991 (Box 60, Folder 46)
  - Young, Jason, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 47)
  - Youngerman, Jack, 1997, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 48)
  - Zakanitch, Robert Rahway, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 49)
  - Zimmerman, Elyn, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 50)
  - Zittel, Andrea, 2005 (Box 60, Folder 51)
  - Zlameeny Insignia Esg. Portrait Project, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 52)
- ACCRETION 2014 - Series II: Administrative Files
  - Art Publications, undated (Box 60, Folder 53)
  - Art-In-Transit Southern California Rapid Transit, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 54)
  - Artists List and Info, undated (Box 60, Folder 55)
  - British Development Trust, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 56)
  - Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 60, Folder 58)
  - Environmental Art: Ecology, 1986, undated (Box 60, Folder 59)
  - Fairmount Park Public Art, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 60)
  - Jay Street and Lawrence Street Subway Stations, undated (Box 60, Folder 61)
  - MTA: Arts for Transit, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 62)
  - Press Releases, 1988-2006 (Box 60, Folder 63)
  - Public Art Master Plan for the City of Milwaukee, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 64)
  - Public Art: Parks and Gardens [1 of 3], 1985-1987 (Box 60, Folder 65)
  - Public Art: Parks and Gardens [2 of 3], 1985-1987 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Public Art: Parks and Gardens [3 of 3], 1985-1987 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Public Art Photos, undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Public Art Press, 1982-2005 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Public Art Press, 1979-1988 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Public Art Press, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Public Art Press, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Public Art Press, 1991-1992 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Public Art Proposals, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Public Art Review, 1985-1991 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Transportation: Public Art Press, 1988-1992, undated (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Urban Public Art, 1988-1989 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Volunteer Lawyers for the Arts, undated (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - World's Fairs, 1981-1983 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- ACCRETION 2014 - Series III: Data Storage
  - Beuhler, Launa, undated; ID: 171.3.0037 (Box 55, Folder 25, Media ID: 171.3.0037)
  - Fabre, Jan, undated; ID: 171.3.0038 (Box 55, Folder 26, Media ID: 171.3.0038)
  - Ferre, Nina, undated; ID: 171.3.0039 (Box 55, Folder 27, Media ID: 171.3.0039)
  - Held, Al, 2005; ID: 171.3.0040 (Box 55, Folder 28, Media ID: 171.3.0040)
  - Poirier, Anne and Patrick, 1997-2000; ID: 171.3.0041 (Box 55, Folder 29, Media ID: 171.3.0041)
- ACCRETION 2014 - Series IV: Media
  - City Arts Segments produced by Kathy Brew and Roberto Guerra, undated; ID: 171.0030 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0030)
    Duration: unknown.
    City Arts Segments produced by Kathy Brew + Roberto Guerra
    - School's Out at PS1 - For the First Time (solo shows) - Artists Space
  - Maureen Connor Composite of 5 Tapes, 1990-1993; ID: 171.0031 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0031)
    Maureen Connor
    Composite tape - 5 documentations of installations - Please refer to list.
  - Maureen Connor "Dancing Lessons", 1995; ID: 171.0032 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0032)
    Maureen Connor "Dancing Lessons" 1995 - Documentation of installation
  - Maureen Connor "Peripheral Vision", undated; ID: 171.0033 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0033)
    Duration: 15 minutes
    15 min. - loop - each sec 1 min., 30 sec. Maureen Connor "Peripheral Vision" Video component of Installation - Please view w/slide
  - Hakone Sculpture Garden, undated; ID: 171.0034 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0034)
    Duration: 16 minutes
    United States Department of the Interior Office of the Secretary 2800 Cottage Way Sacramento, California 95825 Official Business, Penalty for Private Use, $300
  - Douglas Hollis "Waterworks", 2001; ID: 171.0035 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0035)
  - Nancy Holt "Art in the Public Eye: The Making of Dark Star Park", 1988; ID: 171.0036 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0036)
    Duration: 33 minutes
    Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz ART IN THE PUBLIC EYE: The Making of Dark Star Park Nancy Holt 33 min. 1988 166 Bank St. #5D New York, NY 10014 212-929-1947
  - Jane Kaufman Tape #1, undated; ID: 171.0037 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0037)
  - Jane Kaufman Tape #2, undated; ID: 171.0038 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0038)
  - Jane Kaufman Tape #3, undated; ID: 171.0039 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0039)
    Original format: VHS Duration: unknown
  - Jane Kaufman, undated; ID: 171.004 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.004)
    Jane Kaufman Artist 151 West 18th Street New York, NY 10011 USA (212) 924-2693
  - Anna Valentina Murch Selected Works, undated; ID: 171.0041 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0041)
    Selected Works by Anna Valentina Murch Producer and Editor: David Kwan Writer and Editor: Louise Steinman Funded by a Faculty Development Grant from Mills College, Oakland, California
    Anna Valentina Murch 499 Alabama Street, Studio 306 San Francisco, CA 94110 TEL: 415-431-4889 FAX: 415-554-0548 FAX: 415-826-7856 avmurch@earthlink.net
  - "A Penny on The Dollar", November 27, 1994; ID: 171.0042 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0042)
    "A Penny on The Dollar" (Public Art In Kansas City, MO., Seattle, WA., and New York City) From "Sunday Morning," with Charles Osgood, CBS-Tv, Sun. Nov. 27, 1994
  - Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz, April 30, 1993; ID: 171.0043 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0043)
    Duration: 2 minutes; 10 minutes
    JOYCE 1 min 36 sec; 9 min 51 sec JPS - Apr. 30 1993, Fukuoka TV INT.
  - Santa Fe Arts Commission "Public Art in a Multi Cultural Society: On Common Ground", 1991; ID: 171.0045; 5 media elements 1/4" audiocassette (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0045)
    Original format: 1/4" audiocassettes
    #10A
    THE POLITICS OF STYLE. Moderator: Robert Turner; Panel: Joe Traugott, Ron Adams, Sebastian, Joyce Schwartz, Suzan Harjo.
    Pt. 1
    10/31, 11/3, 1991.
    ART IN PUBLIC PLACES CONFERENCE
    OFC Discussion???
    #2
    NATIVE AMERICAN EXPRESSION, Richard Hill.
    ART IN PUBLIC PLACE CONFERENCE
    #3
    San Diego, California - Moderator: MaLin Wilson; Panel: Gail Goldman, Roberto Salas, Christina Estrada.
    #9
    PUBLIC ART IN SPAIN: TRADITIONS AND TRENDS, Dr. Josep-Maria Montaner.
  - Dorothea Rockburne "Northern Sky Southern Sky", 1993; ID: 171.0046 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0046)
    Northern Sky Southern Sky (Sony Installation), 1993.
  - Dorothea Rockburne "The Virtues of GOod Government", 1996; ID: 171.0047 (Box 62, Media ID: 171.0047)
    Dorothea Rockburne "The Virtues of Good Government" Installation at the US Federal Courthouse at Porgland ME, 1996.
- ACCRETION 2014 - OVERSIZE Series I: Artist Files
  - Arman: "Cascades", February 1997 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Buren, Daniel: "The Buren Times", 25 March-8 June, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Francis, Sam, April-May 1987 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Held, Al: Poster, 20 November-3 January, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Kozloff, Joyce: Macquette Tokyo Project, undated (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Madsen, Loren, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1 July-5 October, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Nagel, Andres - Proposals for Park Avenue, undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Oppenheim, Dennis: "Formula Compound", undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Skulptur. Projekte in Munster 97, 22 June-28 September, 1997 (Folder 13)
  - Van Hoydon, undated (Box 63, Folder 6)